G. D. Hsiung papers
Medical Historical Library, Harvey Cushing / John Hay Whitney Medical Library
- Abstracts, Presentations, and Workshops, Series VI
  - Workshops, 1975-1997; Subseries 3
    - 1997 Symposium on Clinical Virology and Bacteriology (Taiwan) - Correspondence, 1996-1997 (Box 23, Folder 6)
      The symposium was held on March 15-16, 1997 in Tainan, Taiwan under the auspices of the National Cheng Kung University Medical College. Hsiung arrived on March 4, 1997 and returned in early April. The trip included a visit to Beijing.
    - 1997 Symposium on Clinical Virology and Bacteriology (Taiwan) - Itinerary (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - 1997 Symposium on Clinical Virology and Bacteriology (Taiwan) - Lectures (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - 1997 Symposium on Clinical Virology and Bacteriology (Taiwan) -- Miscellaneous (Box 23, Folder 9)
      Includes issues of the Pathology Newsletter, National Cheng Kung University Medical Center.
    - 1997 October: ATCC Diagnostic Virology Workshop, Rockville, Maryland (Box 23, Folder 10)
- Conferences/Meetings, Series VII
  Folders may contain correspondence, meeting programs, G. D. Hisung's abstracts and presentations, and minutes of the meetings or groups held in conjunction with the meeting. Folders may overlap Lectures/Presentations.
  - American Society for Microbiology Annual Meeting 1984 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - American Society for Microbiology Branch Meeting 1985 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - American Society for Microbiology Annual Meeting 1995 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - American Society for Virology Annual Meeting 1991 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - American Society for Virology Annual Meeting 1992 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - American Society for Virology Annual Meeting 1993 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - American Society for Virology Annual Meeting 1994 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - American Society for Virology Annual Meeting 1995 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - American Type Culture Collection Registry Council 1962 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - American Type Culture Collection Registry Council 1963 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - American Type Culture Collection Registry Council 1964 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Antivirals Congress 1988 (Finland) (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Australian Society of Microbiology 1992 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Cell Culture for Virus Identification-An Update Seminar 1993 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Chautauqua Research and Development Meeting 1993 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    Meeting for all VAMC researchers in New England and New York
  - Chautauqua Research and Development Meeting 1994 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    Meeting for all VA researchers in New England and New York; Includes poster "Virology Reference Laboratory: Ten Years of Service to Veterans"
  - Clinical Virology Symposium 1985-1988 (Box 24, Folder 17)
    The annual Clinical Virology Symposium was held in conjunction with the annual meeting of the Pan American Group for Rapid Viral Diagnosis.
  - Clinical Virology Symposium 1989 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Clinical Virology Symposium 1990 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Clinical Virology Symposium 1991 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Clinical Virology Symposium 1992 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Clinical Virology Symposium 1993 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Clinical Virology Symposium 1994 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Clinical Virology Symposium 1995 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Clinical Virology Symposium 1996 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Clinical Virology Symposium 1997 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Clinical Virology Symposium 1998 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Clinical Virology Symposium 1999 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Clinical Virology Symposium 2000 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Clinical Virology Symposium 2001 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - INCSTAR DNA Infectious Disease Technology Focus Panel 1996 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Infectious Disease Society of America Annual Meeting 1989 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Infectious Disease Society of America Annual Meeting 1991 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - International Antiviral Symposium, Taiwan 1990 (Box 25, Folder 10)
    Conference "International Antiviral Symposium: Clinical, Pharmacological and Basic Aspects" held in Taipei, Taiwan from June 18-20, 1990
  - International Conference on Antiviral Research 1988 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - International Conference on Antiviral Research 1991 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - International Congress of Virology 1990 (Berlin) (Box 25, Folder 13)
    Conference in Berlin, Germany from August 24-31, 1990; includes abstracts
  - International Congress of Virology (Israel) 1996 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - International Cytomegalovirus Workshop 1989 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - International Symposium on Research of Antiviral Drugs 1992 (Beijing) (Box 25, Folder 16)
    Conference in Beijing, China from November 5-7, 1992; includes the abstract for Dr. Hsiung's presentation
  - Interscience Conference on Antimicrobial Agents and Chemotherapy (ICAAC) 1989 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Interscience Conference on Antimicrobial Agents and Chemotherapy (ICAAC) 1990 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Interscience Conference on Antimicrobial Agents and Chemotherapy (ICAAC) 1991 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Interscience Conference on Antimicrobial Agents and Chemotherapy (ICAAC) 1992 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Interscience Conference on Antimicrobial Agents and Chemotherapy (ICAAC) 1997 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - International Symposium on Viral and Chlamydial Infections (Taiwan), 1999 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    Folder contains only an annotated program. For earlier versions of this conference in which Hsiung led or co-led a workshop, see Workshops.
  - Scandinavian Virus Symposium 1989 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    Conference held in Reykjavik, Iceland on May 30-June 2, 1989; Dr. Hsiung presented "Laboratory Diagnosis of Viral Infections."
  - Southern Association for Clinical Microbiology 1993 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    Lecture given for conference at Vanderbilt University in Nashville, Tennessee on September 14, 1994.
- Published Articles/Reprints, 1950-2006; Series VIII
  This series contains Hsiung's copies of her published articles numbered sequentially. Besides the lists at the end of this series, see Curriculum Vitae in Box 1.
  - Articles, 1950-1954 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    Reprints #1-6
  - Articles, 1955-1959 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    Numbered #7-#18
  - Articles, 1960-1961 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    Reprints #19-25
  - Articles, 1962-1964 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    Reprints #26-37,39
  - Articles, 1965 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    Reprints #41-47
  - Articles, 1966-1967 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    Reprints #48-54
  - Articles, 1967-1968 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    Reprints #55-64
  - Articles, 1969-1970 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    Reprints #65-72
  - Articles, 1971 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    Reprints #73-79
  - Articles, 1972 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    Reprints #80-84
  - Articles, 1973 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    Reprints #86-90 (reprint #87 labelled "Dr. Green", reprint #89 printed in 1974 but recorded by Hsiung as #89)
  - Articles, 1973-1974 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    Reprints #91-99
  - Articles, 1975-1976 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    Reprints #100-113 (one copy of #102 labelled "for corrections" and "all corrected")
  - Articles, 1977 (Box 27, Folder 14)
    Reprints #114-121
  - Articles, 1978 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    Reprints #122-132 (not including #127-130)
  - Articles, 1979 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    Reprints #133-139
  - Articles, 1980 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    Reprints #140-147
  - Articles, 1981 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    Reprints #148-154
  - Articles, 1982 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    Reprints #156-165
  - Articles, 1983 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    Reprints #166-171 (not including #169)
  - Articles, 1984 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    Reprints #180-191 (not including #186)
  - Articles, 1985-1986 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    Reprints #192-205 (not including #197, 198, 201, 202)
  - Articles, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    Reprints #207-215
  - Articles, 1988-1989 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    Reprints #216-221
  - Articles, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    Reprints #222-226
  - Articles, 1990-1991 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    Reprints #227-230
  - Articles, 1992-1995 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    Reprints #232-234, 244, 246
  - Publication list, 1995 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    Comprehensive publication list for G.D. Hsiung as of January 27, 1995
  - Publication lists, 2000 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Publication lists by topic (Box 28, Folder 14)
    Contains lists of publications sorted by Diagnostic Virology, Guinea Pig Herpes-Like Virus, Guinea Pig Retrovirus, and Guinea Pig Cytomegalovirus Infection, compiled by G.D. Hsiung
- Manuscripts, Series IX
  - Submitted Articles, Subseries 1
    Folders may contain drafts of the manuscript, correspondence with the journal editors, peer reviews of the manuscript, photographic illustrations, handwritten tables, and notes. No attempt has been made to correlate these folders with published articles.
    - "Isolation of a Herpes-like Virus from Leukemia Susceptible Strain 2 Inbred Guinea Pigs", 1969 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - "Productive and Abortive Growth of an Equine Cytomegalovirus in Equine and Hamster Cells", 1970 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - "The Purification of Guinea Pig Herpes-Like Virus and Characterization of its Structural Proteins", 1972-1974 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - "Studies of Lymphoid Tissues from Normal and Leukemic Guinea Pigs Infected with Herpes and/or C-Type Viruses", 1974 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - "Latent Herpesvirus Infections in the Brain and Trigeminal Ganglion of Guinea Pigs", 1975 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - "Non-Productive Infection of Hamster Cells with a Guinea Pig Herpesvirus", 1975 (Box 29, Folder 6)
      Folder labelled "Reject"
    - "Comparison of Two Plaque Assay Systems for Testing Antiviral Agents Against Herpes Simplex Virus Types 1 and 2", 1978 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - "The Use of Plaque Assays for Testing AIU and AIC Against Herpes Simplex Virus Strains", 1978 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - "Rapid and Accurate Viral Diagnosis", 1980-1986 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - "Effect of Acyclovir on Lymphotropic Guinea Pig Herpes-Like Virus Replication In Vitro and In Vivo", 1981 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - "Lymphadenopathy During Cytomegalovirus Induced Mononucleosis in Guinea Pigs", 1981-1985 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - "Detection of Viral Genomes in Cultured Cells and Paraffin-Embedded Tissue Sections using Biotin Labeled Hybridization Probes", 1982 (Box 29, Folder 12)
      Folder contains a letter from David Brigati, the senior author of the manuscript, to Enzo Biochemical, Inc. strongly criticizing an article by Lenore Gardner from the company.
    - "Genital Herpes: Pathogenesis and Chemotherapy in the Guinea Pig Model", 1982-1983 (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - "Effect of 2'-Fluoroarabinosides, FIAC, FMAU, and FIAU on Cytomegalovirus Replication", 1983 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - "Effect of CP-20,961 on Genital Herpes in Guinea Pigs", 1983 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - "Prophylactic and Therapeutic Treatment with Acyclovir of Genital Herpes in the Guinea Pig", 1983 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - "The Anti-Viral Activity of CP-20,961 against Herpes Simplex Viruses in Vitro", 1983-1984 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - "Fluoropyrimidine Treatment of Primary Acute Genital Herpes in Guinea Pigs", 1983-1984 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - "Laboratory Diagnosis of Herpes Simplex Virus Types 1 and 2 Infections", 1983-1984 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - "Complement-Requiring Neutralizing Antibody in Guinea Pigs with Primary and Recurrent Genital Herpes", 1984 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - "Diagnostic Virology: From Animals to Automation", 1984 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - "Depression of responses to T and B cell mitogens during acute infection with cytomegalovirus in the guinea pig", 1984 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - "Lymphoproliferative Changes Induced by Infection with a Lymphotropic Guinea Pig Herpesvirus", 1984 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - "Transmission of Maternal Cytomegalovirus Specific Immunity in the Guinea Pig", 1984 (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - "New Concepts in Diagnostic Virology", 1984-1986 (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - "Primary Isolation of Viruses", 1984-1986 (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - "Comparison of Immunofluorescence Using Commercial Monoclonal Antibodies with Biochemical and Biological Techniques for Typing Clinical Herpes Simplex Virus Isolates", 1985 (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - "Inbred Guinea Pig Model of Intrauterine Infection with Cytomegalovirus", 1985 (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - "The Placenta as a Site of Cytomegalovirus Infection in the Guinea Pig", 1985 (Box 30, Folder 16)
      Authors: Brigitte P. Griffith, Stanley R. McCormick, Caroline K. Y. Fong, Jacquelyn T. Lavallee, Helen L. Lucia, and Elizabeth Goff
      Acknowledgement to the Virology Laboratory, Veterans Administration Medical Center, West Haven, CT.
    - "Quantitation of IgG and IgM Antibodies Against Cytomegalovirus in Donor Blood", 1985 (Box 30, Folder 17)
    - "Antiviral Effect of 9-(1,3 Dihydroxy-2-Propoxy-Methyl) Guanine Against Cytomegalovirus Infection in a Guinea Pig", 1985-1986 (Box 30, Folder 18)
    - "Comparison of In Situ Hybridization and Immunological Staining with Cytopathy for Detection and Identification of Herpes Simplex Virus Infection in Cultured Cells", 1985-1986 (Box 30, Folder 19)
    - "Effect of BW1117 Against Cytomegalovirus Infection in the Guinea Pig Model: An In Vitro Study", 1985-1986 (Box 30, Folder 20)
    - "Herpesviruses and Retroviruses of Guinea Pigs", 1985-1986 (Box 30, Folder 21)
    - "Rapid Viral Diagnosis", 1985-1986 (Box 30, Folder 22)
    - "Detection of Guinea Pig Cytomegalovirus Nucleic Acids in Cultured Cells with Biotin-labelled Hybridization Probes", 1986 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - "Direct Detection of Genital Herpes Simplex Virus Infection in the Guinea Pig Model with Monoclonal Antibodies", 1986 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - "Effect of Cyclosporine-A on Acute Infection of Guinea Pigs with a Lymphotropic Virus", 1986 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - "Replication of Human Adenoviruses in Guinea Pig Embryo Cells: An Ultrastructural Study", 1986 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - "Cyclophosphamide Immunosuppression During Lymphotropic Herpesvirus Infection in the Guinea Pig Model", 1986-1987 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - "Double Labeling Using Immunogold-Silver Staining and Avidin-Biotin Immunoperoxidase Staining of SIgG+ Cells Harboring a Lymphotropic Herpesvirus", 1986-1987 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - "Effect of Cyclosporine-A Immunosuppression on Primary Lymphotropic Herpesvirus Infection in the Guinea Pig ", 1986-1987 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - "Effect of Herpes Simplex Virus Concentration in Clinical Specimens on its Rapid Detection in Four Cell Culture Systems", 1986-1987 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - "Efficacy of Topical Fluoropyrimidines for the Treatment of Genital Herpes Simplex Virus Type 2 Infections in the Guinea Pig Model", 1986-1988 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - "Meningoencephalitis Associated with Adenovirus in Previously Healthy Adults", 1986-1988 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - "A False Positive HIV Antibody Reaction Due to Transfusion-Induced HLA-DR4 Sensitization", 1986-1989 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - "Perspectives on Retroviruses and Acquired Immune Deficiency Syndrome", 1987 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - "Efficacy of S26308 Against Guinea Pig Cytomegalovirus Infection", 1987-1988 (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - "Quantitation of Antibody Titers to Cytomegalovirus and Human Immunodeficiency Virus in AIDS/ARC Patients and in Blood Donors", 1987-1988 (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - "Double Labeling of SIgG+ Cells Harboring a Lymphotropic Herpesvirus by Avidin Biotincomplex Immunoperoxidase and Immunogold Silver Staining Techniques", 1987-1990 (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - "An Evaluation of New Antiviral Agents: The Need for Standardizations", 1988 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - "Antiviral Effect of Compound 164 on Guinea Pig Cytomegalovirus Infection", 1988-1989 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - "Activities of Two New Antiviral Agents against Guinea Pig Lymphotropic Herpesvirus Infection in Vitro", 1989 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - "Evaluation of New Antiviral Agents: I. In Vitro Perspective", 1989 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - "Evaluation of New Antiviral Agents: II. The Use of Animal Models", 1989 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - "The Impact of Cell Culture Sensitivity on Rapid Viral Diagnosis: A Historical Perspective", 1989 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - "Studies on Two New Antiviral Agents Against Guinea Pig Lymphotropic Herpesvirus Infection in Vitro", 1989 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - "Activity of HPMPC Against Guinea Pig Cytomegalovirus Infection in Cultured Cells and in Guinea Pigs", 1989-1990 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - "Combined Antiviral Effects of Paired Nucleosides Against Guinea Pig Cytomegalovirus Replication in Vitro", 1990 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - "Antagonistic Antiviral Effect and Synergistic Cytotoxicity of DHPG/AZT Against CMV Infection in Cultured Cells and in Guinea Pigs", 1991 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - "Combined Antiviral Effects of 2'-nor-cGMP and Ganciclovir against Acute Cytomegalovirus Infection in Guinea Pigs", 1991 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - "Zidovudine Antagonizes the Antiviral Effects of Ganciclovir Against CMV Infection in Cultured Cells and in Guinea Pigs", 1992 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - "Medical Microbiology," Chap. 59, in G. D. Hsiung, Diagnostic Virology, 1995 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Mysteries and Miracles (1995), Subseries 2
    These folders relate to the publication of G. D. Hsiung, Mysteries and Miracles: Personal Recollections in Clinical and Diagnostic Virology. Amsterdam: Elsevier, 1995.
    - Correspondence, 1993-1996 (Box 33, Folder 1)
      Folder Includes correspondence with Vantage Press and Yale University Press. The book was published by Elsevier (Amsterdam) in 1995.
    - Dedication to Joseph L. Melnick, 1994 (Box 33, Folder 2)
      Folder contains correspondence about Hsiung's dedication of the first chapter of her book to her mentor, Joseph L. Melnick, in honor of his 80th birthday, as well as about the broader celebration of Melnick's birthday.
    - First Draft, Part One, 1993 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - First Draft, Part Two, 1993 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Second Draft (Box 33, Folder 5)
      Autobiographical account written in pencil on lined paper.
    - Final Draft, Part One, 1994 September (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Final Draft, Part Two, 1994 September (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Diagnostic Virology, Subseries 3
    G. D. Hsiung published four editions of her major textbook with Yale University Press. These are:
    G. D. Hsiung in collaboration with J. R. [J. R. Henderson], Diagnostic Virology (1964).
    G. D. Hsiung, Diagnostic Virology: An Illustrated Handbook, revised and enlarged edition (1973).
    G. D. Hsiung in collaboration with Caroline K.Y. Fong, Diagnostic virology Illustrated by Light and Electron Microscopy, 3rd edition (1982)
    G.D. Hsiung, Caroline K.Y. Fong, and Marie L. Landry, Hsiung's Diagnostic Virology as Illustrated by Light and Electron Microscopy, fourth edition (1994).
    - Diagnostic Virology, 1st Edition: Part 1 (Box 33, Folder 8)
      Files contain mimeographed typescripts with photographs pasted in.
    - Diagnostic Virology, 1st Edition: Part 2 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Diagnostic Virology, 1st Edition: Part 3 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Diagnostic Virology, 1st Edition: Part 4 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - Diagnostic Virology, 1st Edition: Part 5 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - Diagnostic Virology, 3rd Edition: Correspondence (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - Diagnostic Virology, 3rd edition: Promotional Materials (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - Diagnostic Virology, 4th Edition: Correspondence, 1992 (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - Diagnostic Virology, 4th Edition: Correspondence, 1993 (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - Diagnostic Virology, 4th Edition: Correspondence, 1994 (Box 33, Folder 17)
    - Diagnostic Virology, 4th Edition: Reviews (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Photographs for publications, Subseries 4
    - Illustrations for Schoentag, Fong, and Hsiung on Reovirus (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Illustrations for Tscholl and Hsiung, Equine Herpes and Bovine Leucocytes (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Diagnostic Virology: Cover, General trends, classification, etc. (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Diagnostic Virology: Virus Isolation and Identification (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Diagnostic Virology: Virus Assay (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Diagnostic Virology: Immunofluorescence/ ELISA-EIA (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Diagnostic Virology: Hemagglutination Inhibition, Complement Fixation (Box 34, Folder 7)
      Originally labeled 10 and 11 which refer to chapters of the book.
    - Diagnostic Virology: Molecular Biology Technique (Box 34, Folder 8)
      Originally labeled 12.
    - Diagnostic Virology: Electron Microscopy (Box 34, Folder 9)
      Originally 13.
    - Diagnostic Virology: Entero Viruses (Box 34, Folder 10)
      Originally 14.
    - Diagnostic Virology: Myxoviridae (Box 34, Folder 11)
      Originally 15.
    - Diagnostic Virology: Measles (Box 34, Folder 12)
      Originally 16.
    - Diagnostic Virology: Rubella (Box 34, Folder 13)
      Originally 17.
    - Diagnostic Virology: Reo Rota Viruses (Box 34, Folder 14)
      Originally 18.
    - Diagnostic Virology: HIV - Extra Figures (Box 34, Folder 15)
      Originally 20.
    - Diagnostic Virology: Adenoviridae (Box 34, Folder 16)
      Originally 21.
    - Diagnostic Virology: Herpesviridae (Box 34, Folder 17)
      Originally 22.
    - Diagnostic Virology: Papoviridae (Box 34, Folder 18)
      Originally 24.
    - Diagnostic Virology: Parvoviridae (Box 34, Folder 19)
      Originally 25.
    - Diagnostic Virology: Hepatitis Viruses, 1992 (Box 34, Folder 20)
      Originally 26.
    - Diagnostic Virology: Arboviruses (Box 34, Folder 21)
      Originally 27.
    - Diagnostic Virology: Media, Cell Culture, etc. (Box 34, Folder 22)
    - Diagnostic Virology: Endogenous Viruses Cell Cultures (Box 34, Folder 23)
      Originally 29.
    - Diagnostic Virology: CPE Lymphotropic Effect (Box 34, Folder 24)
    - Diagnostic Virology: 2nd Edition, 1972 (Box 34, Folder 25)
    - Diagnostic Virology: 2nd, 3rd Editions (Box 34, Folder 26)
    - Diagnostic Virology: 3rd Edition, 1982 (Box 34, Folder 27)
    - Diagnostic Virology: Photos Removed from 3rd Edition (Box 34, Folder 28)
    - Diagnostic Virology: 4th Edition (Box 34, Folder 29)
    - Diagnostic Virology: Possible Illustrations for the Cover of the 4th Edition (Box 34, Folder 30)
    - Mysteries and Miracles, 1995 (Box 34, Folder 31)
    - "Studies on Two Antiviral Agents Against G.P. Lymphotropic HIV" (Box 34, Folder 32)
      Five diagrams.
- Miscellaneous, Series X
  - Photograph books/scrapbooks of people and conferences, Subseries 1
    These are three-ring notebooks with magnetic photograph pages containing mostly photographs of Hsiung and others. They document laboratory parties, meetings attended, student presentations at meetings, and some of the Clinical Virology Seminars she led. They thus expand on the materials in earlier series.
    - Becton-Dickinson Award scrapbook (disbound), 1983-1986 (Box 35)
      Disbound by archivist since the scrapbook was made of poor materials and already falling apart. The American Society for Microbiology awarded the Becton Dickinson Award, a top honor, to G. D. Hsiung in 1983. See Box 1, Folder 17.
      - Album photograph of G. D. Hsiung, 1983 (Box 35, Folder 1)
        Congratulatory card that was on the cover of the scrapbook. It shows G. D. Hsung surrounded by research images. Inside, it was signed by five members of the Institut Basel fur Mikrobiolgie und Hygiene.
      - American Society for Microbiology press release and announcement, 1983 (Box 35, Folder 2)
      - ASM meeting, New Orleans, 1983 (Box 35, Folder 3)
        Folder contains a photograph of Hsiung in the hotel, her acceptance statement for the award, and an invitation to a reception and buffet.
      - Letters of congratulation from peers (Box 35, Folder 4)
      - Cards of congratulation (Box 35, Folder 5)
      - Other announcements of award (Box 35, Folder 6)
      - Photograph of G.D. Hsiung used for Becton-Dickinson Award, 1983 (Box 35, Folder 7)
      - Surprise party at the VA, 1983 (Box 35, Folder 8)